Fear your past... it will find you
Shallow Ground is a horror film directed by Sheldon Wilson.
A naked teenage boy covered in blood appears at a remote sheriff's station
one year after the brutal unsolved murder of a local girl.
Now Sheriff Jack Shepherd, guilt ridden over the girl's murder, must confront his own demons
as he desperately searches for the boy's true identity and possible victims.
Little does Jack realize that he has started down a path that will
bring him face to face with an unthinkable horror.
Before sunrise the living will pay for the pain the dead have suffered.
Jack Sheppard, played by Timothy V. Murphy.
Laura Russell, played by Lindsey Stoddart.
Boy, played by Rocky Marquette.
Stuart Dempsey, played by Stan Kirsch.
Helen Reedy, played by Patty McCormack.
Darby Owens, played by Natalie Avital.
Shallow Ground is a 2004 horror film written and directed
by Sheldon Wilson and starring Timothy V.
Murphy, Stan Kirsch, Lindsey Stoddart, Patty McCormack an Rocky Marquette.
Its plot follows a teenager covered in blood who
appears at a police station holding a knife.
It was released on DVD in June 2005 in the United States.
The tone is dark.